infodog.com 2012-12-29

# Privacy Statement for infodog.com

## Privacy Statement for infodog.com

Infodog, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: infodog.com. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site's dog show entry form and Winners and Bragging Rights program requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Furthermore, by use of the MB-F Web Sites, you agree to grant MB-F the right to disclose to third parties certain registration data about user and service membership in the aggregate; however, such disclosures will exclude your name, mailing address, email address, account and phone number, unless: (1) you expressly authorize and direct MB-F, or any other person that you may specifically designate to disclose such information through the Service as provided by the Service or (2) MB-F is required to disclose such information by any applicable law or legal process served on MB-F. 

Our site uses discussion forums, which require users to register before posting a message. The user id for this registration process is the user's email address. This address is available for people to access when they post a message. 

This site contains links to other sites. infodog.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our site also uses an order form from time to time for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These security measures include an active hardware/software firewall to prevent unauthorized access to the infodog.com servers and databases, 128-bit encryption with secure socket layers for the safe transmission of credit card data over the Internet, and a 24-hour-a-day alarm security system for the onsite premises where the infodog.com servers and data physically reside. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [mbf@infodog.com](mailto:mbf@infodog.com)
  2. You can call the following telephone number: 336 379 9352
  3. The following question with a check box appears on our site where users enter dog shows and subscribe to our Winners and Bragging Rights system as well as on the printed dog show entry forms included with MB-F, Inc. superintended dog shows: From time to time Infodog sends carefully selected email messages to the fancy. These messages only pertain to useful information and products Infodog feels are in the best interest of purebred dogs. If you DO NOT wish to receive these messages, please check this box. 

## Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [mbf@infodog.com](mailto:mbf@infodog.com)
  2. visit [infodog.com](http://www.infodog.com/)
  3. send mail to the following postal address: 
P.O. Box 22107 Greensboro, NC 27420 
  4. call the following telephone number: 336 379 9352

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Infodog, Inc. P.O. Box 22107 Greensboro, NC 27410
